<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-15T03:44:32-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wysc</title><subtitle>For students striving to be better, Wysc is the study Discord server that delivers a cohesive, global online studying experience as the premier edu-social cafe based Discord server.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Launch of Wysc Events</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-events.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Launch of Wysc Events" /><published>2019-07-26T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-events</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-events.html">&lt;p&gt;We’re really excited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are social creatures. We seek connectivity with others and find joy in hanging out together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the launch of &lt;!--more--&gt;the Wysc Events homepage, users who are inspired to create a group event will be able to create their own event pages with Wysc, expanding their ability to reach new users through the networks we’ve built into the system — including automatic notifications to Wysc and abilities such as scheduling posts, RSS feeds, and emails through WordPress. So you can focus more on hosting an event, not trying to tell people that it exists in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To qualify for applying, events must have been independently held at least three times consistently and consecutively in #group-events in order to show demand. Once accepted, hosts will be able to start posting directly to the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please bear with us as we continue to improve upon this system as it rolls out to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing the diverse number of ideas and events that are generated, and to hosting a forum for the users, by the users!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
Wysc Staff ☕&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We’re really excited. People are social creatures. We seek connectivity with others and find joy in hanging out together. With the launch of</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wysc Blog Release</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-blog-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wysc Blog Release" /><published>2019-07-04T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-blog-release</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/wysc-blog-release.html">&lt;p&gt;Wysc is proud to announce significant progress in expanding our website’s ability to be a central information hub for the Wysc experience!&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the release of the Wysc Blog, new information will be easily accessible in the event of a service being unavailable or to convey important announcements and updates regarding our service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Future updates to Wysc will exist primarily on our website, with a brief overview and link to our website in our Discord server. This will allow us to be more flexible in providing more detailed information and more varied forms of media moving forward, as well as lengthier pieces of documentation that may be relevant to users that Discord currently prohibits due to a maximum character limit and lack of proper formatting tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you find this new system easier to navigate compared to our previous system, and look forward to continued improvements throughout our June 2019 Server Revamp!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
Wysc Staff ☕&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Wysc is proud to announce significant progress in expanding our website’s ability to be a central information hub for the Wysc experience!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Misbehaving Users</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/misbehaving-users.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Misbehaving Users" /><published>2019-06-29T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/misbehaving-users</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/misbehaving-users.html">&lt;p&gt;Wysc highly values the openness and freedom of its users to participate in a free forum of information exchange in a casual environment. In fact&lt;!--more--&gt;, what sets us apart exclusively from other study servers is our much more relaxed approach at moderation in comparison to the more heavy-handed tactics other study servers resort to when users misbehave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During our pilot expansion program promoting our server on Disboard and other server promotion sites, we have discovered that there has been a need to continue adapting our server’s infrastructure to the imminent danger of users abusing our open platform to spread malicious messages unrelated to our core focus on study and music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to this situation, Wysc Staff has opened up quarantine permissions for all Tree role members (highest activity role) by typing the d.nsfw @user command. This will allow the community the tools necessary to seize control of a malicious situation during the hours when Wysc Staff is offline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope this approach will help balance usability with moderation, and thank you for continuing to be a part of Wysc during our time of evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;
Wysc Staff ☕&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Wysc highly values the openness and freedom of its users to participate in a free forum of information exchange in a casual environment. In fact</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">June 2019 Wysc Server Revamp</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/june-2019-wysc-server-revamp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="June 2019 Wysc Server Revamp" /><published>2019-06-18T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/june-2019-wysc-server-revamp</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/june-2019-wysc-server-revamp.html">&lt;p&gt;As students across the world arrive at a lull in their studies, Wysc is proud to begin a series of renovations to the server that fundamentally change &lt;!--more--&gt;how we seek to operate from today forth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For one, we are no longer named ‘Work・Studying・Chilling’, more colloquially referred to as ‘WSC’. From late June 2019 onwards, we will be rebranding as ‘Wysc’. This decision was taken as a step forward to develop a stronger brand name for the service we provide, while still maintaining a sense of familiarity for our existing community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All aspects of Wysc are currently undergoing a thorough revamp, from the server experience to the companion website. A new simplified permissions system is under development, as well as a new feed-powered experience across Wysc. This will mean more evergreen content on a more sustainable trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wysc’s goal is to provide a laid-back environment free of overbearing constraints for patrons to interact at their own discretion. To that end, we’re in this with you for the long haul, and we’re committed to delivering a satisfactory service in a way that is scalable and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New server and website features will be rolled out incrementally throughout June 2019 and into the summer as they become ready. We hope you’re as excited as we are!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information is listed at our new website, https://wysc.bookmark.com/.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you, &lt;br /&gt;
- Wysc Staff&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As students across the world arrive at a lull in their studies, Wysc is proud to begin a series of renovations to the server that fundamentally change</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/0319-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2019-03-19T11:15:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/0319-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2019/0319-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d just like to give a shoutout to our longtime members who are still here and supporting WSC in our journey forward. If you’ve been a member since early 2018 you should notice a new “WSC Veteran” role added to your user :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also working on some big things at the moment, so keep in touch – we’ll be back soon with more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep wyscing on,
-  WSC Staff&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hey everyone!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0713-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2018-07-13T05:09:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0713-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0713-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey yall, nothing important or anything, but here are some statistics on WSC’s activity for the past 30 days!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;▫️ WSC has served over 200 messages daily on average! &lt;br /&gt;
▫️ The top 10 most active users accounted for 85% of WSC activity, consisting of over 15k messages &lt;br /&gt;
▫️ WSC has now hit 350 members, with 65 active Discord users online daily on average &lt;br /&gt;
▫️ Over 87% of WSC voice activity occurs in the Study Room voice channel, indicating a heavy lean towards study-related activities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your continued patronage in WSC as we continue to seek to grow and expand our services to more users!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ WSC Staff ]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hey yall, nothing important or anything, but here are some statistics on WSC’s activity for the past 30 days!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0615-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2018-06-15T22:08:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0615-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0615-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Lots of new channels added for the June 2018 WSC Update!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✨💼 Work category now fully launched!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#career - ask about job/internship advice, help, tips, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#resources - relaunched channel for sharing helpful resources and tips&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#life - ever wish high school taught you how to do taxes or other practical life skills? join others in this new channel!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✨📚 New channels added under Studying!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#self-intro - relaunched introductions channel for finding study partners!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#study-center - early release yielded great results. General study area for exams, college apps, and other questions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#accountability - new “Accountability” feature introduced by our mod Trevish! List your to-do tasks here and check them off as you complete them. Encourage your study partner to complete their tasks, and strive to complete your own as well!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;#business - relaunched business, economics, and government channel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;@everyone Hope you enjoy the new channels, if you want to suggest something to include in the server, drop it in #lounge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ WSC Staff ]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Lots of new channels added for the June 2018 WSC Update!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0512-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2018-05-12T14:08:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0512-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0512-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Changed WSC’s logo to Blurple! (temporary change) Official blurb below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re taking part in a community event called Project Blurple! To celebrate Discord’s 3rd anniversary, our server and many others are making our logos blurple! The aim of the event is to get as many servers and users as possible to switch to a blurple themed logo! You can join in too and get you and your servers involved by heading over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.gg/qEmKyCf&quot;&gt;https://discord.gg/qEmKyCf&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;margin-bottom:2em;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;You've been invited to join a server&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/icons/412754940885467146/5766a662d858b24ee743385b672306af.png?size=256&quot; width=&quot;64px&quot; alt=&quot;Project Blurple&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flex-1xMQg5 flex-1O1GKY vertical-V37hAW flex-1O1GKY directionColumn-35P_nr justifyCenter-3D2jYp alignStretch-DpGPf3 noWrap-3jynv6 guildInfo-1STtYi&quot; style=&quot;flex: 1 1 auto;&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;guildName-2hvnt_ marginBottom4-2qk4Hy medium-zmzTW- weightSemiBold-1WYsXZ&quot;&gt;Project Blurple&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;guildDetail-1nRKNE small-29zrCQ weightSemiBold-1WYsXZ&quot;&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;flex-1xMQg5 flex-1O1GKY horizontal-1ae9ci horizontal-2EEEnY flex-1O1GKY directionRow-3v3tfG justifyStart-2NDFzi alignCenter-1dQNNs noWrap-3jynv6&quot; style=&quot;flex: 0 1 auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;statusOnline-8PnF5L status-2L8Zc7&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;onlineCount-w6_WmG&quot;&gt;4,798 Online&lt;/span&gt; &lt;i class=&quot;statusOffline-37RKt7 status-2L8Zc7&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;29,407 Members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/358786581785608202/444969860502650890/unknown.png&quot; alt=&quot;Project Blurple&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/358786581785608202/445135538593333258/unknown.png&quot; alt=&quot;Project Blurple giveaway&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(giveaways are in the Project Blurple server, invite link above)
HAPPY BDAYY DISCORDD!! 🍰🎂😊&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ WSC Staff ]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Changed WSC’s logo to Blurple! (temporary change) Official blurb below:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0209-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2018-02-09T08:29:00-08:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0209-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0209-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi @everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of our server partners, Studious Students, had an unfortunate incident where their server was hacked and deleted. WSC would like to extend our dearest condolences, and wishes a speedy recovery for Studious Students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The invite for the new server will be up in #server-partners once the new Studious Students server is fully completed. For now, if there are any questions, comments, or concerns from the community, feel free to discuss them in #lounge or #cafe :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to a continued partnership between our servers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Regards, &lt;br /&gt;
Sakura 🌸, on behalf of WSC Staff&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;updated 2018-02-13&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📣 | Announcement for Studious Students server @everyone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;&lt;strong&gt;⚠ Note: There is an unofficial copy of the server that is currently being run by another user.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;It is not the original server and we do not recommend you join it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/del&gt; &lt;em&gt;The incident has been resolved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;strong&gt;Studious Students&lt;/strong&gt; server is now up and ready! &lt;strong&gt;Please be wary of false copies&lt;/strong&gt;; the link below was directly sent to us by @[redacted], the admin of the old server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.gg/gU9GdNG&quot;&gt;https://discord.gg/gU9GdNG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;margin-bottom:2em;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5&gt;You've been invited to join a server&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/icons/332244720736534530/feb6ae8901c9d7e42bd29d496f50316f.png?size=256&quot; width=&quot;64px&quot; alt=&quot;studious students&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;flex-1xMQg5 flex-1O1GKY vertical-V37hAW flex-1O1GKY directionColumn-35P_nr justifyCenter-3D2jYp alignStretch-DpGPf3 noWrap-3jynv6 guildInfo-1STtYi&quot; style=&quot;flex: 1 1 auto;&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;guildName-2hvnt_ marginBottom4-2qk4Hy medium-zmzTW- weightSemiBold-1WYsXZ&quot;&gt;studious students&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;guildDetail-1nRKNE small-29zrCQ weightSemiBold-1WYsXZ&quot;&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;flex-1xMQg5 flex-1O1GKY horizontal-1ae9ci horizontal-2EEEnY flex-1O1GKY directionRow-3v3tfG justifyStart-2NDFzi alignCenter-1dQNNs noWrap-3jynv6&quot; style=&quot;flex: 0 1 auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;statusOnline-8PnF5L status-2L8Zc7&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;onlineCount-w6_WmG&quot;&gt;122 Online&lt;/span&gt; &lt;i class=&quot;statusOffline-37RKt7 status-2L8Zc7&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;766 Members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ WSC Staff ]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hi @everyone,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WSC update</title><link href="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0106-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WSC update" /><published>2018-01-06T11:08:00-08:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T04:12:58-08:00</updated><id>https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0106-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wysc.netlify.com/blog/2018/0106-update.html">&lt;p&gt;Just another flyer on the announcement board:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lt;@360069875504513035&amp;gt;#7514 Now Banned - Read on if you got a DM from her&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jennifer has messaged a small portion of our users requesting for help writing an essay for her. Because we take incidences of mass DM’ing users seriously, as well as the implications that can arise from assisting with plagiarism, we have taken actions to notify Jennifer of her infractions and have thus banned her from WSC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We apologize for any inconveniences this may have caused, and would like to take the chance and remind everyone to keep this option off for increased privacy and security!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/358786581785608202/399112078792720384/unknown.png&quot; alt=&quot;Discord privacy settings - Allow Direct Messages turned off&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ WSC Staff ]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Just another flyer on the announcement board:</summary></entry></feed>